It's me. Anyone here?
Ben geldim, kimse var mı?
Is anyone here?
Kimse var mı?
Johan…
Johan.
At the Red Rose Mansion…
Kırmızı Güllü Malikâne'de…
many people drank that wine.
…pek çok insan o şaraptan içti.
Don't you worry.
Endişelenme.
Look, I'm drinking it too.
Bak, ben de içiyorum.
Where are the bodyguards who should already be here?
Buraya gelmesi gereken korumalar nerede?
Why…
Bebek'i
did you kill The Baby?
neden öldürdün?
I thought we were working together.
Birlikte çalıştığımızı sanıyordum.
You said you would help us
Bize yardım edeceğini söylemiştin.
We would find your sister and give her--
-Kız kardeşini bulup ona… -Her şey plana göre gidiyor.
Your sister…
Kız kardeşin…
We've already captured your sister.
Kız kardeşini çoktan yakaladık.
If anything happens to me, your sister is dead.
Bana bir şey olursa kız kardeşin ölür. Bu işin sonu istediğin gibi olmayacak.
Listen! Everything will go according to my plans!
Beni dinle, her şey benim planıma göre gidiyor!
What am I?
Ben neyim?
The monster inside me wasn't inside me.
İçimdeki canavar içimde değildi.
It was outside of me.
Dışımdaydı.
What are you trying to say?
Ne demeye çalışıyorsun?
Franz Bonaparta…
Franz Bonaparta…
He's alive, isn't he?
…hayatta, değil mi?
Sorry to bother you so late, Nina Fortner.
Bu saatte rahatsız ediyorum, kusura bakma Nina Fortner.
Ms. Fortner?
Bayan Fortner.
Nina Fortner?
Nina Fortner.
Don't move!
Kıpırdamayın!
Who told you to come here?
Sizi kim gönderdi?
Now I see.
Şimdi anladım.
As The Baby said, you're not just some young woman.
Bebek'in dediği gibi, sen sıradan bir genç kadın değilsin.
The Baby?
Bebek mi?
The Baby ordered you to come and get me?
Buraya gelip beni götürmenizi Bebek mi emretti?
No. The Baby is dead.
-Hayır. Bebek öldü. -Öldü mü?
The person who wants us to collect you is Petr Čapek.
Seni almamızı isteyen kişi Petr Čapek.
With you as his hostage, he'll be safe.
Seni rehin alırsa güvende olacak.
Čapek?
Čapek mi?
Take me to him.
Beni ona götürün.
I'll go with you to Petr Čapek.
Sizinle Petr Čapek'in yanına geleceğim.
We're from the police.
Polisiz.
We're here to search the home of Milan Kolasch, the suspect
Milan Kolasch'ın evini aramaya geldik.
in the shooting at the Rödelheim Convention Center.
Kendisi Rödelheim Fuar Merkezi saldırısında şüpheli.
Get started.
Başlayın.
Out of the way!
Çekilin!
Go on! Move!
Hadi, çekilin.
Is this Kolasch's room?
Kolasch'ın odası burası mı?
It appears so.
Öyle görünüyor.
The police will be here soon to search the house.
Polis birazdan gelip evi arayacak.
I have to leave now.
Hemen gitmem gerek.
Is Milan…
Milan…
Is Milan truly dead?
Milan gerçekten öldü mü?
Milan died… for our sakes.
Milan bizim uğrumuza öldü.
Čapek killed our relatives.
Čapek akrabalarımızı öldürdü.
He was killed trying to get vengeance for our sakes.
Milan bizim intikamımızı almaya çalışırken öldürüldü.
Vengeance…
İntikam…
We'll get vengeance!
İntikamımızı alacağız.
Don't you dare!
Sakın ha!
Don't think about doing that!
-İntikam almayı aklınızdan geçirmeyin -Ama Milan bunun için…
This isn't what Milan wanted.
Milan'ın istediği bu değil.
Vengeance breeds vengeance.
İntikamdan intikam doğar.
It just keeps repeating itself.
Tekrar edip durur.
Milan didn't want you to think that way.
Milan böyle düşünmenizi istemedi.
Someone had to stop this.
Birinin buna bir son vermesi gerek.
Milan wanted to put an end to it.
Milan buna bir son vermek istedi.
What was it that Milan wanted?
Milan ne istemişti?
He wanted… all of us to visit each other's home countries together.
Birbirimizin ülkelerine birlikte gitmemizi istemişti.
Then study hard and you'll make that dream come true someday.
O zaman çok çalışın ve bu hayalinizi bir gün gerçekleştirin.
Thank you for all you've done, Mustafa.
Tüm yardımların için teşekkürler Mustafa.
Minh.
Minh.
Suleiman, thank you for the delicious meals.
Süleyman, enfes yemekler için teşekkürler.
Dr. Tenma, don't tell me you're…
Dr. Tenma, yoksa sen de…
We've found a lot of documents concerning this man Petr Čapek.
Petr Čapek'le ilgili bir sürü belge bulduk.
Yes. It seems that Milan Kolasch was targeting
Evet, Milan Kolasch'ın hedefinde
this Čapek fellow.
Čapek denen adam varmış sanırım.
Find this man immediately and question--
Derhâl bu adamı bul ve sorgula…
Inspector!
Dedektif!
The leader of the right-wing radicals, The Baby,
Sağcı radikallerin lideri, Bebek,
was found murdered at the Kaiser Hotel.
Kaiser Otel'de ölü bulundu.
Someone must…
Birisi onu…
I must… stop him.
Ben onu durdurmalıyım.
That's the young man who's often been with Petr Čapek at this hotel.
Petr Čapek'le bu otelde sık sık görüşen genç adam bu.
Is that the devil's apprentice?
İblisin çırağı o mu?
Follow that car.
Şu aracı takip et.
Johan?
Johan.
Are you here, Johan?
Burada mısın Johan?
Where have you been, Johan?
Nerelerdeydin Johan?
Aren't you… Eva?
Sen Eva değil misin?
Where is he?
Nerede o?
Where is Johan?
Johan nerede?
Mr. Čapek, we've brought Nina.
Bay Čapek, Nina'yı getirdik.
Mr. Čapek…
Bay Čapek…
Petr… Čapek…
Petr Čapek.
Come with me. Don't be afraid.
Benimle gel, korkma.
Stop, dammit!
Dursana lan!
Which one are you? Johan?
Sen hangisisin? Johan mısın?
His sister?
Kız kardeşi misin?
I guess now it doesn't matter which one you are.
Sanırım artık hangisi olduğunun bir önemi yok.
Johan let me live…
Johan canımı bağışladı
because the one who will kill me…
çünkü canımı alacak kişi…
is his sister.
…Johan'ın kız kardeşi.
Everything is going to plan.
Her şey plana göre ilerliyor.
But whose? Mine?
Ama kimin planına göre? Benim planıma göre mi,
Or Johan's?
Johan'ın planına göre mi?
Whose plan…
Bu plan
is this?
kimin planı?
Hurry up… and kill me.
Elini çabuk tut, öldür beni.
So, Johan was here.
Johan buradaydı demek.
Where did he go?
Nereye gitti?
Take me there.
Beni onun yanına götür.
Where is Johan now?
Johan şu an nerede?
It's pitch black.
Zifiri karanlık.
I'm scared.
Korkuyorum.
I want to get out of here right now.
Hemen buradan çıkmak istiyorum.
If we leave now…
Şimdi gidersem…
Do you think it's still going on?
Sence hâlâ devam ediyor mu?
The killing.
Cinayet.
If I had not introduced you…
O partide seni…
at that party…
…o iblisle
to that devil…
tanıştırmasaydım…
If I hadn't done that…
Bunu yapmasaydım…
Martin…
…Martin…
Martin would…
Martin…
have never died.
…hiç ölmezdi.
Fine. Now, hold on.
Peki, dur bakalım.
Where's Johan?
Johan nerede?
I don't know.
Bilmiyorum.
I wish I knew where he was too.
Keşke bilseydim ama.
Just calm down.
Sakin ol.
I've been watching this apartment for two weeks.
İki haftadır bu daireyi izliyorum.
He never showed up here.
Buraya hiç gelmedi.
Where else is he staying?
Başka nerede kalıyor?
I just told you, I don't know!
Söyledim ya, bilmiyorum.
I mean it.
Ciddiyim.
My ear!
Kulağım!
I'm serious about this.
Benim şakam yok.
It hurts!
Acıyor!
Next time, it won't just be your ear,
Bir dahakine kulakla kalmayacağım
Christof Sievernich.
Christof Sievernich.
I looked into you.
Seni araştırdım.
But I already knew all about your father,
Ama babanı, merhum Ernest Sievernich'i
the late Ernest Sievernich.
zaten tanıyordum.
The head of the Sievernich Group, the leading conglomerate in Frankfurt,
Frankfurt'un, belki de Almanya'nın
if not all of Germany.
öncü holdingi Sievernich Grup'un başkanı.
It's hard to believe you're the heir to that empire.
O imparatorluğun varisi olduğuna inanmak güç.
Petr Čapek introduced you to Johan.
Seni Johan'la Petr Čapek tanıştırdı.
What are you planning to do?
Ne yapmayı planlıyorsun?
Look how much I'm bleeding! Let me get patched up.
Ne kadar kan kaybettiğime bak. Bırak da pansuman yapayım.
Now that I introduced you to that devil, what are you people starting?
Ben seni o iblisle tanıştırdıktan sonra ne yapmaya başlıyorsunuz?
You got it all wrong.
Yanlış anlamışsın.
What do you mean?
Nasıl yani?
Čapek believes that he brought the two of us together,
Čapek ikimizi bir araya getirdiğini düşünüyor.
but Johan and I…
ama Johan'la
have known each other for a long time.
uzun zaman önce tanışmıştık.
What?
Ne?
Čapek doesn't know…
10 yıl önce
that over a decade ago, we were friends in East Berlin.
Doğu Berlin'de arkadaş olduğumuzu Čapek bilmiyor.
Over a decade ago in East Berlin?
10 yıl önce Doğu Berlin'de mi?
I was adopted by Sievernich.
Sievernich beni evlatlık aldı
But that's not quite accurate.
ama tam da böyle olmadı.
I was sold to him by a black market merchant.
Bir karaborsa tüccarı beni ona sattı.
Johan and I met one another in East Berlin…
Johan'la Doğu Berlin'de tanıştık.
at Kinderheim 511.
511. Yetimhane'de.
511?
511 mi?
That's where we met.
Orada tanıştık.
We were the survivors.
Hayatta kalanlardık.
He and I were the only survivors.
Sadece ikimiz hayatta kaldık.
I'm scared.
Korkuyorum.
I'm starving.
Açlıktan öleceğim.
I have to pee.
Çişim var.
Do you think… the killing is over?
Birbirlerini öldürmeyi bırakmışlar mıdır sizce?
Do you think they're all dead?
Sizce hepsi ölmüş müdür?
Why don't you go out and look?
Çıkıp baksanıza.
It will be fine.
Bir şey olmaz.
It's quiet out there now.
Dışarısı çok sessiz.
It'll be just fine. Go have a look.
Bir şey olmaz. Çıkıp bir bakın.
You'll lose your mind if you stay here.
Burada kalırsanız aklınızı kaçıracaksınız.
I… I'll go and look.
Ben gidip bir bakayım.
If it's all right, come back and tell us.
Sorun yoksa geri gelip bize söyle.
Okay.
Tamam.
I'm not sure why but everyone at Kinderheim 511 went mad that day.
511. Yetimhane'de herkes neden aklını kaçırdı bilmiyorum.
Not just the children,
Sadece çocuklar değil,
but even the teachers started killing each other.
öğretmenler bile birbirini öldürmeye başladı.
He hasn't come back.
Daha dönmedi.
-He ran away. -What?
-Kaçtı. -Ne?
He left us behind and ran away.
Bizi geride bırakıp kaçtı.
You're kidding!
Dalga geçme.
He just wanted to save himself.
Sadece kendini kurtarmak istedi.
Do you think so?
Öyle mi diyorsun?
If you think I'm lying, then go out and look.
Yalan söylediğimi düşünüyorsan çık da bak.
I bet right now that jerk has found himself a nice hot meal.
O pislik şu an kendine sıcak bir yemek bulmuştur.
A hot meal?
Sıcak bir yemek mi?
I'll take a little look around.
Etrafa bir bakayım.
You won't betray me, right?
Bana ihanet etmezsin, değil mi?
Of course not.
Etmem tabii.
But he never came back either.
Ama o da hiç dönmedi.
I'll stay hidden forever.
Sonsuza dek burada saklanacağım.
As I sat there hungry and thirsty…
Orada aç ve susuz otururken
I fell in and out of light sleep.
uyuklayıp duruyordum.
Will I die here?
Burada ölecek miyim?
That's when…
İşte o an
he appeared.
o geldi.
It's just you and me.
Sadece ikimiz kaldık.
I have a plan.
Bir planım var.
Was that Johan?
Johan mıydı o?
Čapek says it's all his plan, but that's such a joke.
Čapek her şeyin onun planı olduğunu söylüyor
We talked it over a lot when we were kids.
Çocukken bunu çok konuştuk.
What is it? What is his plan?
Ne? Johan'ın planı ne?
Do you want to hear it?
Duymak istiyor musun?
Well, you see…
Peki…
How dare you!
Bu ne cüret?
How dare you shoot my ear off!
Kulağımı ne cüretle vurursun?
To become a politician, my face means everything!
Siyasetçi olmam için yüzüm her şeyden daha önemli!
So how dare you!
Bu ne cüret?
I will control the world!
Ben dünyayı yöneteceğim.
Isn't that right?
Öyle değil mi?
Working with Johan, I will make the world mine!
Johan'la el ele vererek dünyaya sahip olacağım!
Do you get that?
Anlıyor musun?
How will I replace my ear?
Kulağımı nasıl düzelteceğim?
How dare you interfere with our plan!
Planımıza ne cüretle burnunu sokarsın?
How dare you!
Ne cüretle?
Throw down your gun!
Silahını at!
Kenzo!
Kenzo!
Johan told me…
Johan, kız kardeşi geldiğinde
that when his sister comes, to tell her where he is.
ona Johan'ın yerini söylememi istedi.
He then said that you would kill me.
Sonra senin beni öldüreceğini söyledi.
But why didn't you kill me?
Beni neden öldürmedin?
Have you gotten all your memories back?
Anıların aklına geldi mi?
Yes.
Evet.
Then…
O zaman
why don't you kill me?
beni neden öldürmüyorsun?
You must be overflowing with hatred, anger…
Kin, öfke ve hüzünle dolup taşıyor olmalısın,
and sadness, right?
öyle değil mi?
What are we?
Neyiz biz?
You know, don't you?
Biliyorsun, değil mi?
-I once heard… -Huh?
-Siz ikizlerin… -Ne?
the story of how you two twins were born.
…doğum hikâyenizi bir keresinde duymuştum.
Subtitle translation by: Brian Athey
Alt yazı çevirmeni: Ömür Gencer